

Kiran Pandey

Graphics & UI/UX Designer

Contact Me

- pandeykiran14@gmail.com
- +91-8054717938 / 8360235480
- Sector 49, Faridabad, Haryana,
- http://tiny.cc/kiranP
- Bē www.behance.net/kiranpandey2



http://tiny.cc/portfoliokiran

Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Canva
- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Corel Draw
- Adobe Premier Pro

Education Background

- Maximus Auto Desk, Delhi Diploma In Web & Graphics Design
- D.D.U University, Gorakhpur Post Graduate In Political Science
- D.D.U University, Gorakhpur Masters In Political Science And Hindi

About Me

Work From Home Only

I'm Kiran, I can help your company create stunning visuals. As someone who has worked in graphic and UI/UX design, I know what brands need to capture their audience's attention. With my powerful design skills, I have the right background for your brand's needs. I'm an interdisciplinary designer who's been creating experiences for the web for 3+ years. I am expert in Adobe Photoshop, Canva, Adobe XD, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Corel Draw, Adobe Premier Pro, Filmora... I can't wait to learn about your brand's design needs!

Professional Experience

New Source Hub | Graphics & Ui/Ux Designer 2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Analyze client requirement and prepare design
- Convert Low Quality Designs To High Quality For Printing
- Make design for Souvenir Shop
- Make Catalogues And Boucher
- Make and Update Product Catalogue
- Convert Designs into printable form in Corel draw
- Make design Mockups
- Make Social Media Posts
- Make UI/UX Design For Company Website

ZEDD LABZ | Graphics & Ui/Ux Designer 2022 - 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Analyse client requirement and prepare design
- Look at designs from Google and identify trends
- Make design as per client requirements
- Make UI/UX For App and website as per client requirement
- Make Social Media Posts As Per Client Requirement
- Make Social Media Stories As Per Client Requirement
- Make Tourist Videos As Per Client Requirements
- Make Course Social Media Posts As Per Client Requirements
- Make Videos As Per Client Requirements

CombatFit Wears LLP | Graphics Designer 2021 - 2022

Ava Infotech | Ui/Ux & Graphics Designer 2020 - 2021